when you're creating Word documents
there may be situations where you need
to insert images on chart to convey
information or to enhance the appearance
of the document there is an opportunity
for you to practice this and the first
thing you need to do is to download the
two files that will work so on this
video the first one is called balloon
JPEG so if you just click on that and
then right-click on it and select see a
picture ours and then that will give you
the opportunity to save it to a suitable
location
I've already see if that into the wp2
folder and for the spreadsheet on it
slightly different so when you click on
that it will give you the option at the
bottom to open see if or cancel or if
you click on the little arrow you can
see of ours
so if I click see of ours again that
brings me up with the word processing
unit folder and I will just see if that
Annette and that's done so I can then
close that so when I come to my word
document that I want to insert the
images or a charts bring that up and for
this one on this letter I'm going to
insert an image at the top of the
document it's important to make sure
that you placed occurs on the right
position because that is where the
actual image will be inserted no if I
clicked I insert the image now it would
automatically Pierce it directly in
front of the base myth so I know there's
a lane space above so I'll just go there
and I'm going to go to insert that's a
picture from this device and if it's in
my documents in the IT course and in the
word processing for that so if I know
double click on that that will insert
the image as you can see the image is
quite large and needs to be formatted as
mentioned earlier on this page in the
course there are a variety of tools and
features that you can use to format your
picture this only appears when you have
the picture open the picture highlighted
as you can see with the the bars around
the site if I
clicked away from the picture they will
go back to the home tab so to edit the
picture I need to make sure that I have
it selected and the toolbar will change
to the picture formatting bar the only
thing I need to do with the picture is
actually reduce the size and to keep the
aspect ratio correct I will do that from
the corner so if I select one of the
corners and just drag that in as you can
see that is reducing the size but also
keeping the aspect ratio correct so I
don't you start to I'm happy with that a
little bit more and that's it now as you
can see because I've done that the
actual text has gone off the bottom of
the page so again I do need to adjust
that a little bit more and that's not
faint